http://www.orioncaraudio.com/content/6-privacy-policy

Dealer Forms
International Dealers
Search:
Where To Buy:
------ Select a Product ------
AmplifiersDiscontinued2018 Cobalt 2 Channel Amplifiers-CB1200.2-CB2500.2-CB4500.22018 Cobalt 4 Channel Amplifiers-CB4000.4-CB1200.4-CB2000.42018 Cobalt Class D Monochannel Amplifiers-CB2500.1D-CB4500.1D-CB1500.1DXTR 2 Channel Amp-XTR250.2-XTR600.2-XTR1200.2-XTR2000.2-XTR500.2-XTR1500.2-XTR2500.2-XTR750.2XTR 4 Channel Amp-XTR 350.4-XTR 600.4-XTR 800.4-XTR 1200.4-XTR500.4-XTR750.4-XTR1000.4-XTR1700.4-XTR2500.4XTR Ultra Efficient Class D Mono Channel-XTR15001 (3000 Watts Max Power) -XTR1400.1D-XTR2200.1D-XTR3700.1D-XTR1000.1D-XTR650.1D2018 XTR Dz SERIES-XTR1500.1Dz-XTR2500.1DzHCCA SPL COMPETITION AMPLIFIERSHCCA ULTRA EFFICIENT AMPLIFIERSHCCA SPLX COMPETITION AMPLIFIERS-HCCA3000.1DSPLX-HCCA12500.1DSPLX-HCCA17000.1DSPLX-HCCA5000.1DSPLXTwo Channel Amplifiers-ZT1200.2-ZT2000.2-ZT3000.2-ZT5000.2Four Channel Amplifiers-ZT1500.4-ZT2500.4-ZT5000.4Five Channel Amplifiers-ZO6000.5Class D Amplifiers-ZT2000.1D-ZT3000.1D-ZT8000.1D-ZT5000.1DSubwoofersCobalt Subwoofers-Cobalt CO104D-Cobalt CO104S-Cobalt CO124D-Cobalt CO124S-Cobalt CO154D-Cobalt CO154SCobalt Single Subwoofer Enclosures2020 COBALT CT SUBWOOFER-CT-124S-CT-124DXTR Subwoofers-XTR102D -XTR104D -XTR122D -XTR124D-XTR152D -XTR154DXTR Ntense SubwoofersXTR Xtreme SubwoofersXTRPRO Series Subwoofers: -XTRPRO 102D-XTRPRO 104D-XTRPRO 122D-XTRPRO 124D-XTRPRO 152D-XTRPRO 154DXTRPRO Black Coil Recone Kit - XTRPRO102DRK-XTRPRO104DRK-XTRPRO122DRK-XTRPRO124DRK-XTRPRO152DRK-XTRPRO154DRKHCCA Subwoofers-HCCA 102 -HCCA 104 -HCCA 122 -HCCA 124-HCCA 152 -HCCA 154-HCCA 152SPL -HCCA 154SPLHCCA Black Coil Recone Kit-HCCA 104RK-HCCA 124RK-HCCA 154RK-HCCA 122RK-HCCA 152RK-HCCA 102RK -HCCA152SPLCK -HCCA154SPLCK 2018 HCCA SPLX SUBWOOFERS-HCCA121SPLX- HCCA122SPLX-HCCA181SPLX-HCCA182SPLXZtreet Subwoofers-ZTW104S- ZTW124S- ZTW124D-ZTW104DCoaxialsCobalt
Coaxials-Cobalt CO40-Cobalt CO46-Cobalt CO52-Cobalt CO57-Cobalt CO60-Cobalt CO65-Cobalt CO68-Cobalt CO69-Cobalt CO653-Cobalt CO693-Cobalt CO603-Cobalt CO652-CT-653Cobalt Component Kit w/ Crossover-Cobalt CO652C-Cobalt CO652C2020 COBALT CT COAXIALS-CT-57-CT-653-CT-693-CT-46-CT-T15-CT-CK525-CT-40-CT-CK655-CT-525XTR Coaxials-XTR40.2-XTR52.2-XTR57.2-XTR60.2-XTR65.2-XTR65.3-XTR68.2-XTR69.2-XTR69.3-XTR46.2-XTR65.2SLZTREET COAXIALS-ZTC-400-ZTC-460-ZTC-525-ZTC-570-ZTC-65SL-ZTC-650-ZTC-653-ZTC-692-ZTC-693-ZTC-52.2CK-ZTC-65.2CK-ZTC-TW105ComponentsCobalt Series Component Systems-CO552 -CO652C -CO400C-CO525CXTR Component Kit w/ Crossover-XTR55.SC-XTR65.SCDiscontinuedHCCA Series Component Systems: -HCCA1002 -HCCA52 -HCCA62 Subwoofer EnclosuresCobalt Single Subwoofer Enclosures: -CO104SBX (Single 10-inch 4 ohm) -CO124SBX (Single 12-inch 4 ohm) -Cobalt CO124SBDVC-2-Cobalt CO124SBV-4DiscontinuedCobalt AccesoriesComplete Kits Power/Interconnect Kits -ORK8 (Power Kit 8 AWG Simple Amp / CCA Spec)-ORK82 (Power Kit 8 AWG Dual Amp / CCA Spec)-ORK4 (Power Kit 4 AWG Simple Amp / CCA Spec)-ORK42 (Power Kit 4 AWG Dual Amp / CCA Spec)Power Kits-ORKC8P (Power Kit 8 AWG Simple Amp / CEA Spec)-ORKC4P (Power Kit 4 AWG Simple Amp / CEA Spec)-ORKC1 (Power Kit 1/0 AWG Simple Amp / CEA Spec)Adapters -ORCMM (RCA Male-Male Interconnect Adapter)-ORCRMF (RCA Right Angle Male-Female Interconnect Adapter)-ORCFF (RCA Female-Female Interconnect Adapter)2 Channel RCA's -ORC3 (3ft RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC12 (12ft RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC16 (16ft RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)2 Channel Pro Series RCA's -ORCP (1.5ft PRO Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORCPR (1.5ft PRO Series Right Angle RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC3P (3ft PRO Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC3PR (3ft PRO Series Right Angle RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC12P (12ft PRO Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC12PR (12ft PRO Series Right Angle RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC16P (16ft PRO Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC16PR (16ft PRO Series Right Angle RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)6 Channel Pro Series RCA's -ORCP4 (1.5ft PRO Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC3P4 (3ft PRO Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC12P4 (12ft PRO Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC16P4 (16ft PRO Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)2 Channel Expert Series RCA's -ORCE (1.5ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC3E (3ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC12E (12ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)4 Channel Expert Series RCA's -ORC16E (16ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC34 (1.5ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC3E4 (3ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC12E4 (12ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)-ORC16E4 (16ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair)6 Channel Expert Series RCA's -ORC16E6 (16ft Expert Series RCA Side/Side Twisted Pair) Video Cables-ORV (1.5ft Video Cable 75ohm)-ORV3 (3ft Video Cable 75ohm)-ORV10 (10ft Video Cable 75ohm)-ORV16 (16ft Video Cable 75ohm)Battery Terminals -ORBGM (Battery Terminal GM)-ORBGMS (Battery Terminal GM Short)-ORBGML (Battery Terminal GM Long)-ORB (Battery Terminal +/-)-ORBP (Battery Terminal +/- (Premium))Fuse Holders -ORFMANL (Fuse Holder Single Mini ANL)-ORFDMANL (Fuse Holder Dual Mini ANL)-ORFANL14 (Fuse Holder ANL 1/0AWG with 4AWG Reducer In/Out)Distribution Blocks -ORD14 (Distribution Block (1) 1/0AWG In - (4) 4AWG Out)-ORD48 (Distribution Block (1) 4 AWG In - (4) 8AWG Out)Crimp Rings -ORT8 (Crimp Rings 8AWG)-ORT1 (Crimp Rings 1/0AWG)-ORT4 (Crimp Rings 4AWG)-ORG4 (Ground Ring 4AWG)-ORG1 (Ground Ring 1/0AWG)Fuse Holders-OWFHM1414-OWFHM1010-OWFH100HP-OWFHM30204-OWFHM30404Capacitors-ORC1 (Capacitor 1 farad with Distribution Top)-ORC1D (Capacitor 1 farad Digital with Distribution Top)-ORC2D (Capacitor 2 farad Digital with Distribution Top)-ORC5V (Capacitor 5 farad with Volt Meter)-ORC10V (Capacitor 10 farad with Volt Meter)Electronics-ORRPA (Remote Power Adapter)-ORSRA (Speaker Level to RCA Adapter)-ORGLI50 (Ground Loop Isolator 50 Watt)-ORGLI100 (Ground Loop Isolator 100 Watt)-ORLOC60 (Adjustable Line Output Converter 60 Watt)Speaker Wire -ORW1620 (20ft Roll 18AWG Speaker Wire Frosted Blue / CCA Spec)-ORW16 (500ft Spool 16AWG Speaker Wire Frosted Blue / CCA Spec)-ORW12 (250ft Spool 12AWG Speaker Wire Frosted Blue / CCA Spec)-ORWC12 (250ft Spool 12AWG Speaker Wire Frosted Blue / CEA Spec)-ORW9 (100ft Spool 9 Wire Install Cable / CEA Spec)-ORWC16 (500ft Spool 16AWG Speaker Wire Frosted Blue / CCA Spec)Power/Ground Wire -ORW8B (250ft Spool 8AWG Frosted Blue / CCA Spec)-ORW8G (250ft Spool 8AWG Frosted Black / CCA Spec)-ORW4B (100ft Spool 4AWG Frosted Blue / CCA Spec)-ORW4G (100ft Spool 4AWG Frosted Black / CCA Spec)-ORWC4R (100ft Spool 4AWG Frosted Red / CEA Spec)-ORWC4G (100ft Spool 4AWG Frosted Black / CEA Spec)-ORWC8R (250ft Spool 8AWG Frosted Red / CEA Spec)-ORWC8G (250ft Spool 8AWG Frosted Black / CEA Spec)-ORWC1R (50ft Spool 1/0AWG Frosted Red / CEA Spec)-ORWC1G (50ft Spool 1/0AWG Frosted Black / CEA Spec)Fuses -ORFMA30 (Fuse Mini ANL 30AMP 4 Pack)-ORFMA40 (Fuse Mini ANL 40AMP 4 Pack)-ORFMA50 (Fuse Mini ANL 50AMP 4 Pack)-ORFMA60 (Fuse Mini ANL 60AMP 4 Pack)-ORFMA70 (Fuse Mini ANL 70AMP 4 Pack)-ORFMA80 (Fuse Mini ANL 80AMP 4 Pack)-ORFMA100 (Fuse Mini ANL 100AMP 4 Pack)-ORFMA120 (Fuse Mini ANL 120AMP 4 Pack)-ORFA100 (Fuse ANL 100AMP 2 Pack)-ORFA120 (Fuse ANL 120AMP 2 Pack)-ORFA150 (Fuse ANL 150AMP 2 Pack)-ORFA200 (Fuse ANL 200AMP 2 Pack)-ORFM30 (Fuse MAXI 30AMP 4 Pack)-ORFM40 (Fuse MAXI 40AMP 4 Pack)-ORFM50 (Fuse MAXI 50AMP 4 Pack)-ORFM60 (Fuse MAXI 60AMP 4 Pack)-ORFM70 (Fuse MAXI 70AMP 4 Pack)Remote Bass/Gain Control-RGC2Cobalt Power WireCobalt Speaker Wire-Cobalt S10300PB-Cobalt S12300PB-S14300PB-S16300PB-S181000PB-XL-S161000PB-XLCobalt Complete Amplifier Kit-Cobalt COKIT0-Cobalt COKIT2-Cobalt COKIT4-Cobalt COKIT8Cobalt RCA Wires-Cobalt CR1.0B-Cobalt CR2.0B-Cobalt CR3.0B-Cobalt CRY2M-Cobalt CRY2F-Cobalt CR4.0B-Cobalt CR5.0B-COBALT CR0.5B-COBALT CR6.0BCobalt Fuse Holders-Cobalt FHMF100-Cobalt FHMF80-Cobalt DBF1424-Cobalt DBF1434-Cobalt DBF1444Cobalt Power Ground Dist Block-Cobalt DB1248-Cobalt DB20204-Cobalt DB1044-Cobalt DB2034Cobalt Ring Terminals-Cobalt RT0R-Cobalt RT0B-Cobalt RT4R-Cobalt RT4B-Cobalt RT8R-Cobalt RT8BCobalt Barrier Spade Terminals-Cobalt B4R-Cobalt B4B-Cobalt B8R-Cobalt B8B-Cobalt NS60-Cobalt NS80-Cobalt NS120Cobalt Ground Loop Isolator-Cobalt NS60-Cobalt NS80-Cobalt NS120Cobalt Circuit Breaker-Cobalt CB100A -Cobalt CB250A -Cobalt CB300A -Cobalt CB150A-Cobalt CB200ACobalt Antenna Adaptor-Cobalt CHRA16-Cobalt GMA36-Cobalt VWA16S-Cobalt VWA16L-Cobalt GMA36-Cobalt GMA16Mini ANL Power Dist Block -Cobalt DBF 1424-Cobalt DBF 1434-Cobalt DBF 1444CrossoversXTR Series Crossovers:-XTR-X3R-XTR-X4RTweetersCobalt Bullet Tweeter-Cobalt CTW101-Cobalt CTW125-Cobalt CTW150-Cobalt CTW200-Cobalt CTW400-Cobalt CTW500-Cobalt CTW880H-Cobalt CTW600-Cobalt CTW700-COBALT COTW1-CTW1.7HP-CTW2.0NEOCobalt Bullet Tweeter Coil Kit-CTW101RK-CTW125RK-CTW150RK-CTW200RK-CTW400RK-CTW500RK-CTW600RK-CTW700RK-CTW880HRK-CTW1.7HPRKXTR Bullet Tweeter-XTR XTW250FD -XTR XTW750FD -XTR XTW950FD -XTR XTW350NEXTR Bullet Tweeter Voice Coil Kit-XTR XTR250FDR-XTR XTR350NEK-XTR XTR750FDRK-XTR XTW950FDRKXTR Tweeter-XTR1.00TWHCCA Bullet Tweeter-HCCA TN-1HCCA Bullet Tweeter Voice Coil Kit-HCCA TN1RKMidrangesCSB Series-Cobalt CSB84-Cobalt CSB64CM Series-CM85- CM65-CM105DC Series -CM655DC- CM855DCCT Series-CT-M8-CT-M62017 XTR SERIES XTX FERRITE MAGNET - XTX654-XTX854-XTX1058DC-XTX1054DC-XTX1058-XTX1054-XTX858-XTX6582017 XTR SERIES XSM SLIM FERRITE MAGNET-XSM655SL-XSM805SLOrion Midranges - Discontinued2020 XTR MIDRANGE NEO-XTR-654NEOHCCA Neodymium Series-HCCA 64N-HCCA 68N- HCCA854N-HCCA1054N-HCCA1058NHCCA Neodymium HP Series-HCCA 654NHP-HCCA 658NHP- HCCA854NHP-HCCA1058NHP-HCCA854NHP2018 XPM SERIES
MIDRANGES FERRITE MAGNET-XPM854MBF-XPM858MBF-XPM1054MBF-XPM1058MBF- XPM658MBF-XPM654MBFWired AccesoriesPerformance RCA-PRF-0.5-PRF-1.0-PRF-2.0-PRF-3.0-PRF-4.0-PRF-5.0-PRF-6.0-PRF-Y2MMP-PRF-Y2FFPPremium RCA-XW-0.5-XW-1.0-XW-2.0-XW-3.0-XW-4.0-XW-5.0-XW-6.0-XW-Y2MMP-XW-Y2FFPPremium Complete Amplifier Kits-XWCKO-XWCK4-XWCK8Expert Power and Speaker Wires-EXPPW050B-EXPPW050T-EXPPW4100B-EXPPW4100T-EXPS10200BFuse HoldersANL Fuse Holders-OWFHANL1011A-OWFHANL1022B-OWFHANL2033BA-OWFHANL2044SQ-OWFHANL20DIGIVPower Ground Dist Block -DB10102428-DB20202428Fuses Mini ANL-MA 50-MA 60-MA 80-MA 100-MA 150-MA 200-MA 250Fuses ANL -ANL80-ANL100-ANL150-ANL200-ANL250-ANL300Ring Terminals-RT0-RT4-RT200-RT244Battery Terminal-BT0044Mini ANL Fuse Holder-OWFHM1414-OWFHM1010-OWFH100HP-OWFHM30204-OWFHM30404Converter-W10-2X0-CCBL-W10-2X00-CCBL-W10-2X0-ALBLDriver Kits Driver Kits-XDK04.2AS-XDK03PS- XDK02PS-XDK01PBZtreet AccesoriesZtreet Power Wire-ZPW4100BK-ZPW4100R-ZPW8250BK-ZPW8250RZtreet Speaker Wire-ZSW12400-ZSW181000Ztreet Complete Kit Amplifier-ZA-KIT4-ZA-KIT8AccesoriesXTR COMPLETE KIT -XTRCOPPERKIT0-XTRCOPPERKIT4-XTRCOPPERKIT8XTR POWER WIRE -XPW050F-XPW050R
Home>Privacy policy
Print Page
Email Page
Privacy policy
MD Audio Engineering its subsidiaries and affiliate companies ("MD Audio Engineering") understand that the protection and use of information provided by you to MD Audio Engineering is important to you. MD Audio Engineering is committed to maintaining your privacy. This Privacy Policy Statement sets out our information collection, use and dissemination practices for website (the "Website"). By visiting any of the MD Audio Engineering Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement and hereby grant your consent to collect this information. Please read this Privacy Policy Statement to understand how MD Audio Engineering collects, uses and disseminates information through our Website.What Personal Information About You Does MD Audio Engineering Collect?The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience. Here are the types of information we gather.Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on this Website or give us in any other way. This information includes demographic information and contact information such as names, addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers and email addresses. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features or conduct transactions.Information Automatically Collected: MD Audio Engineering may also automatically collect non-personal information and data through the use of Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to enhance your experience using our Website. Through cookies, a website can recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's access to and use of the Website, and allow a site to track usage behavior. MD Audio Engineering does not use cookies to gather personal information about you. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers.The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of our Website's features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.How is Collected Information Used?We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling your orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.Does MD Audio Engineering Share Information?MD Audio Engineering is not in the business of selling your information to others. We share customer information only as described below. We have controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.
Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: For certain transactions we work closely with our affiliated businesses to package, ship and fulfill your order. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. We may share customer information related to those transactions with third parties.
Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Promotional Offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers you can let us know by sending an email to info@mdaudio.net.
Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy Statement (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that MD Audio Engineering, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Protection of MD Audio Engineering and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of MD Audio Engineering, our shareholders, users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
How Do I Grant Consent?You hereby grant consent for MD Audio Engineering to collect the information as set out in this Privacy Policy Statement. Other than as set out above, you will not receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will not have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. You may withdraw or limit you consent by contacting MD Audio Engineering at info@mdaudio.net.What About Children?It is MD Audio Engineering's intention that our Website be use only by adults. MD Audio Engineering does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use the Website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. MD Audio Engineering does not knowingly send direct mailings to anyone under the age of 16.What About Other Policies and Revisions?If you choose to visit our Website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use which are incorporated herein by reference, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with this policy.
Products Resources
Orion® Products
Owner's Guides
Interactive Demos
Orion® Glossary
HCCA™ SubwooferChallenge
Enclosure Dimensions
Where To Buy
If you are interested in becoming an authorized Orion dealer, please complete this form:
Dealer Enrollment Form
© Copyright 2012 MD AUDIO ENGINEERING INC. All Rights Reserved.
Terms of Use  |
Privacy Policy  |
Site Map
Development by
